const triviaQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Who is the youngest member of the Overwatch organization?',
        options: ['Tracer', 'Winston', 'D.Va', 'Orisa'],
        answer: 'Orisa'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the base that Winston grew up at?',
        options: ['Overwatch', 'Blackwatch', 'Horizon Lunar Colony', 'Recall'],
        answer: 'Horizon Lunar Colony'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Overwatch hero is known for his signature "HAMMER DOWN!" ability?',
        options: ['Reinhardt', 'Roadhog', 'Lucio', 'Junkrat'],
        answer: 'Reinhardt'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the omnics that fought against humanity during the Omnic Crisis?',
        options: ['Null Sector', 'Bastion', 'The Iris', 'The Omniums'],
        answer: 'The Omniums'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which character was known to have assinated omnic spiritual leader Tekhartha Mondatta?',
        options: ['Zenyatta', 'Genji', 'Hanzo', 'Widowmaker'],
        answer: 'Widowmaker'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is known as Lena Oxton?',
        options: ['Tracer', 'Sombra', 'D.Va', 'Widowmaker'],
        answer: 'Tracer'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which overwatch hero did Genji seek peace from before joining overwatch?',
        options: ['Zenyatta', 'Honzo', 'Reinhardt', 'Winston'],
        answer: 'Zenyatta'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was the original leader of Overwatch?',
        options: ['Ana', 'Reaper', 'Winston', 'Soldier: 76'],
        answer: 'Soldier: 76'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Overwatch hero is a former professional gamer?',
        options: ['Sombra', 'D.Va', 'Tracer', 'Genji'],
        answer: 'D.Va'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Overwatch hero leads the notorious Deadlock Gang?',
        options: ['Cassidy', 'Ashe', 'Junkrat', 'Roadhog'],
        answer: 'Ashe'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Overwatch hero was formerly part of the notorious Deadlock Gang?',
        options: ['Cassidy', 'Ashe', 'Junkrat', 'Roadhog'],
        answer: 'Cassidy'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is Gabriel Reyes?',
        options: ['Reaper', 'Soldier 76', 'Baptiste', 'Lucio'],
        answer: 'Reaper'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is formerly the leader of Blackwatch, the covert ops division of overwatch?',
        options: ['Reaper', 'Soldier 76', 'Baptiste', 'Sigma'],
        answer: 'Reaper'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the oldest hero in overwatch 2?',
        options: ['Reinhardt', 'Ana', 'Sigma', 'Zenyatta'],
        answer: 'Sigma'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the terrorist organization that seeks to cause chaos and destruction in the world of Overwatch?',
        options: ['Talon', 'Blackwatch', 'Darkwater', 'Deadlock Gang'],
        answer: 'Talon'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was the original leader of Overwatch?',
        options: ['Ana', 'Reaper', 'Winston', 'Jack Morrison'],
        answer: 'Jack Morrison'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is Reinhardt the godfather of?',
        options: ['D.Va', 'Brigitte', 'Mei', 'Tracer'],
        answer: 'Brigitte'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the leader of Null Sector?',
        options: ['Zenyatta', 'Genji', 'Sigma', 'Ramattra'],
        answer: 'Ramattra'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the daughter of Ana?',
        options: ['Tracer', 'Pharah', 'Sombra', 'Mei'],
        answer: 'Pharah'
    },
    {
        question: 'Whos inventions were crucial to ending the Omnic Crisis and kept Overwatch at the cutting edge' +
            ' of weapons and technology for decades?',
        options: ['Torbjorn', 'Ana', 'D.Va', 'Zenyatta'],
        answer: 'Torbjorn'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the oldest hero in overwatch 2?',
        options: ['Reinhardt', 'Ana', 'Sigma', 'Zenyatta'],
        answer: 'Sigma'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which hero is a champion weightlifter and used their strength to help rebuild their nation?',
        options: ['Winston', 'Doomfist', 'Zarya', 'Reinhardt'],
        answer: 'Zarya'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which champion became the bodyguard of the notorious Junker Queen?',
        options: ['Junkrat', 'Wrecking Ball', 'Roadhog', 'Moira'],
        answer: 'Wrecking Ball'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which champion is one of the worlds most notorious hackers and joined the ranks of Talon?',
        options: ['Symmetra', 'Widowmaker', 'Moira', 'Sombra'],
        answer: 'Sombra'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which champion weaves hard-light architectural constructs, creating buildings and infrastructure from thin air?',
        options: ['Torbjorn', 'Symmetra', 'Sigma', 'Winston'],
        answer: 'Symmetra'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has ruled over all the Junker factions for over a decade?',
        options: ['Moira', 'Roadhog', 'Junker Queen', 'Junkrat'],
        answer: 'Junker Queen'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which champion weaves hard-light architectural constructs, creating buildings and infrastructure from thin air?',
        options: ['Torbjorn', 'Symmetra', 'Sigma', 'Winston'],
        answer: 'Symmetra'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who lead the Shimada ninja clan after his father passed before later abandoning the clan?',
        options: ['Hanzo', 'Genji', 'Lifeweaver', 'Zenyatta'],
        answer: 'Hanzo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Who was stuck in cryostasis for nine years, only to wake up the only survivor at the station?',
        options: ['Moira', 'Ana', 'Symmetra', 'Mei'],
        answer: 'Mei'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which champion was built by an 11 year old genius and successfully repelled an attack from Doomfist?',
        options: ['Ramattra', 'Orisa', 'Zenyatta', 'Echo'],
        answer: 'Orisa'
    },





];

export default triviaQuestions;